Hey, step in the office, right?
We are really excited to have you join our team
here, man.
Yeah, your stats profiles off the
charts. You're going to crush it here.
Job's basically yours.
Just got to take this dumb ethics and compliance test,
but it's very easy.
There's always two obviously wrong
answers and then a right one, right?
So,
for example, should you share classified
materials from Wellington and Stern?
The
answer is obviously
no.
Okay. Yeah,
great. Or another example, uh, Cheryl,
she shows up to the office wearing a low
cut shirt.
Should you comment on her
body?
Not to her.
Well, no, not to anybody.
- That's hilarious.
- She gross.
It's [ __ ] guy, right? You're [ __ ] funny.
Um, you know, uh, technically
we're not supposed to be here when you
take the test, but,
maybe we could
stick around, make sure this thing works
out.
Hello
and welcome to the ethics,
morals, and compliance examination at
Wellington and Stern.
Look at this thing. It's obviously like
super corny.
Yes,
we will be asking you if the actions in
this video
align with the standards here
at Wellington and Stern.
Good luck, and
we hope to see you in our offices soon.
Protocol
Hey guys, that was a long day of working here.
What do you say we get out of here
right now? We can still catch a happy hour.
Well, hold on. I've got to log out
of my computer.
I got classified
documents on this thing.
Classified documents? Marcus, this isn't
NASA.
You don't have to log out. Let's just go
get drunk.
Marcus wants to go to happy hour, but he
has not logged off.
Should he A not
worry about logging off like Calvin said,
B pour coffee on the computer so
no one has access to it?
C log off
correctly even though it may make him
late to the pub.
Right. And obviously the answer is
C.
Totally.
You guys just go
well done. As an
employee at Wellington and Stern,
we
never share classified information.
Outside
We may leave our work at the office, but
not our values.
Sheesh, I made it.
Hey, look who it is. It's Marcus.
It looks like he finally got over his period.
Calvin, that joke is inappropriate and I
would like an apology.
Should Calvin Apologize to Jane?
B. Say
the joke again louder because maybe Jane
didn't hear it.
Or C. Tell Jane to
lighten up and ask her if she's still
with her boyfriend.
That one.
What? What are you doing?
You found that offensive.
Jane, your hair is offensive. It's ugly
as [ __ ] and everybody hates it.
What the [ __ ]
Everybody laughs about it at the office.
I didn't want to tell you, but you came
down here and acted like a [ __ ]
I've never seen this part of the video
before.
Yeah, this is weird.
Speaking of ugly as [ __ ] how's that
boyfriend Jeff ears?
Michelle. Cheryl, get in here. What?
Dude,
you got to check this out.
My relationship with Jeff is none of
your business.
- What the [ __ ]
- Yeah, I know. He clicked one of the
obviously wrong answers.
- Well,
and for your information, Jeff and I
broke up.
Now we're talking business.
Should Calvin A tell Jane he's sorry and
hope she's feeling better?
B tell her Jeff's a [ __ ] anyway,
or C tell her
that if she gave him one chance, he
could make her squirt.
Hell yeah.
Squirt.
what the [ __ ] Jay?
All right, let's wrap this up. We got work tomorrow.
Where you going? Squirts are good.
Should Calvin A. Go home.
B stay and have three more beers.
I mean, obviously go home.
Okay, hold on a sec.
Stay.
No, no,
I'm going to get [ __ ] up now.
Calvin has to pee.
Should he A just go
right there? I mean, what's the big [ __ ] deal?
or B.
Are you pissing on the bar?
no.
You're gone. Let's go. Let's [ __ ] it.
Calvin is drunk and now sad.
Should he A walk home,
B call a taxi,
or C drive the company car home with the
headlights on?
Wait, are you out of your [ __ ] mind?
There we go.
Nope.
- Oh, that's a big no no.
- I've done it.
can't drive after [ __ ] few years.
Should Calvin A slow down,
B pull over and rest up,
or C text Jane to see if he
can get some [ __ ] at the buzzer?
Pull over.
Text Jane.
Hey, Jane. Is Calvin?
What the [ __ ] was that all about earlier?
What the [ __ ]
- Did he just hit someone?
- I've done it.
Hey, buddy. Quit [ __ ] around. What
are you [ __ ] laying down there?
Should Calvin a call the police?
[ __ ]
- Call the police. Call the police.
- He calls the police. He's [ __ ]
Put the body in the trunk.
Get a hamburger.
Oh, [ __ ] Where did these guys come
from?
Should Calvin A. Take Route 1 towards
the airport.
B. 76 West towards the
mall.
Take 76.
He's got to get to the airport
and wait in line for a [ __ ] ticket.
Francis,
if you take 76, they'll close the exits.
Arrogant [ __ ]
The [ __ ] is that?
[ __ ]
Almost [ __ ] made it.
What the [ __ ]
You're surrounded.
Oh [ __ ] These guys are pissed. This
seems pretty serious.
Should Calvin a check the glove box for
the company gun?
There's a gun in the glove box.
You're going to jail, [ __ ] Yeah, I
bet you I don't
just got to shoot at the cops and make a
run for it.
Terrible idea.
Oh, what would you do, Donnie? Huh? I
don't know. Jerk off.
What? He needs to immediately start
building an insanity defense.
Hey, don't you guys think you're [ __ ]
overreacting?
Yeah, look at that [ __ ]
Oh, I'm sorry, Francis. I've never
killed anybody.
Maybe we should ask your
dad what it feels like.
You guys made this whole thing [ __ ] a big deal.
I was not that bad
other than that guy. I hit a guy. I killed a guy.
wait.
- Driver, attention.
- What?
We are willing to let you go under
one condition.
Would you mind sharing your classified
documents from Wellington and Stern?
Should Calvin Hey.
No can do, Kimabis.
That is correct. We never share
confidential information
with anyone who
doesn't work at Wellington and Stern.
Privacy is our top priority.
Congratulations and welcome to the team.
Nice.
You got to get some new [ __ ] dice.